当他跑去康乃狄克、纽约、加州
When he goes to Connecticut, New York and California
他就会违反联邦法
he'll have violated federal law.
还有，他也违反了哈佛法
And by the way, he's in violation of Harvard law.
- 没有什么哈佛法 - 等等
There's no such thing as Harvard law. Wait,
对耶，有的
Yes, there is.
哈佛学生手册
Harvard student handbook.
每位新生都有一本这个
Every freshman is issued one of this.
这里面有写
Somewhere in this book says...
不能窃取其它学生的东西
You can't steal from another student.
这就是我们需要的
This is what we needed.
我们去见桑默斯校长
We're going to Summers.
你根本见不到桑默斯
You can't get a meeting with Larry Summers.
我哥和我，我们付了学费
My brother and I pay tuition at this school,
我们以高分进入本校
we carry a 3.9 GPA at this school,
我们为本校赢过奖杯
We've won trophies for this school